Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic collection 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company.
90 linear feet Extent: 30,000 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The Iconographic Collection spans the years 1848-2005 with the bulk of materials dating between 1940 and 1985, and includes black-and-white and color photographs, negatives, slides, contact sheets, photograph albums, and microfiche. It is an artificial collection created to document the facilities, key events, advertising highlights and corporate culture of the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT). Domestic and international offices are included, with the New York, Chicago and London offices being the most heavily represented. Key executives include James Walter Thompson, Stanley and Helen Landsdowne Resor, Don Johnston, Dan Seymour, Norm Strouse, and E.G. Wilson. Client advertising includes Ford, Kodak, Chesebrough-Pond's, Lever Brothers (Unilever), and Warner-Lambert. Notable photographers whose work appears in the collection include Fabian Bachrach, Ralph Bartholomew, Cecil Beaton, Louise Dahl-Wolfe, Philippe Halsman, Horst P. Horst, George Hurrell, Yousuf Karsh, Baron Adolf de Meyer, Bill Ray, Jean Raeburn, Edward Steichen, Thomas Veres, Brett Weston and Dorothy Wilding. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.00712
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, nitrate negatives and some other items may not be accessible due to preservation concerns.
Additionally, reproduction-quality copies of Pond's Advertising Photographs may not be produced for non-JWT users.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987, with additions in subsequent years.
Collection Overview
The Iconographic Collection spans the years 1848-2005 with the bulk of materials dating between 1940 and 1985, and includes black-and-white and color photographs, negatives, slides, contact sheets, photograph albums, and microfiche. It is an artificial collection created to document the facilities, key events, advertising highlights and corporate culture of the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT). Domestic and international offices are included, with the New York, Chicago and London offices being the most heavily represented. Key executives include James Walter Thompson, Stanley and Helen Landsdowne Resor, Don Johnston, Dan Seymour, Norm Strouse, and E.G. Wilson. Client advertising includes Ford, Kodak, Chesebrough-Pond's, Lever Brothers (Unilever), and Warner-Lambert. Notable photographers whose work appears in the collection include Fabian Bachrach, Ralph Bartholomew, Cecil Beaton, Louise Dahl-Wolfe, Philippe Halsman, Horst P. Horst, George Hurrell, Yousuf Karsh, Baron Adolf de Meyer, Bill Ray, Jean Raeburn, Edward Steichen, Thomas Veres, Brett Weston and Dorothy Wilding.
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into eight series: Corporate Events; Office Photographs; Officers and Staff Photographs; Negatives; Pond's Photographs and Negatives; Slides; Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives; and Oversize Materials.
Corporate Events includes photographs of some of JWT's art and artifact collections as well as of meetings, seminars and anniversary parties of company-wide significance. Office Photographs document interiors and exteriors of JWT's domestic and international office buildings. Officers and Staff Photographs primarily feature senior-level management, but there are also publicity photographs and group portraits of departments, sports teams, and employee outings. Negatives comprise negatives associated with the Corporate Events, Office Photographs, and Officers and Staff Photographs Series. Pond's Photographs and Negatives include portraits of celebrities and socialites taken by leading photographers for Pond's beauty products advertising campaigns. Slides consist primarily of monthly advertising highlights as well as materials assembled for presentations. Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives consist of work performed by Veres under contract to JWT, primarily of company events and staff. Oversize Materials include large-format materials pulled from other series.
Restrictions on Access: Reproduction-quality copies of Pond's Advertising Photographs may not be produced for non-JWT users.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; Chesebrough-Pond's.; Eastman Kodak Company; Ford Motor Company; Lever Brothers and Unilever, ltd; Warner-Lambert Company; Bachrach, Fabian, 1917-; Bartholomew, Ralph, 1907-1985; Beaton, Cecil, 1904-1980; Dahl-Wolfe, Louise; De Meyer, Adolf, Baron, 1868-1949; Halsman, Philippe; Horst, 1906-1999; Hurrell, George, 1904-1992; Johnston, Don, 1927-; Karsh, Yousuf, 1908-2002; Meek, Samuel W. (Samuel Williams), b. 1895; Steichen, Edward, 1879-1973; Strouse, Norman H.; Weston, Brett; Wilding, Dorothy, 1893-1976; Wilson, Edward G., 1909-1993; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- Employees; Advertising agencies -- History; Advertising executives; Advertising -- Photographers; Advertising photography; Commercial photogrqphy; Corporate culture; Photographic albums -- 1890-1960; Photography -- Collections; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Contact sheets; Fashion photographs; Microfiche; Negatives; Photographic albums; Slides; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Materials related to this collection may be found in the following collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files
Domestic Advertisements Collection
International Advertisements Collection
Review Board Records
Don Johnston Papers
Dan Seymour Papers
Norman H. Strouse Papers
Edward G. Wilson Papers
Materials relating to Edward Steichen may be located in:
Colin Dawkins Papers
Lucile Turnbach Platt Papers
In addition, materials relating to Pond's advertising may be located in:
Nan Findlow Papers
Howard H. Henderson Papers
Shirley F. Woodell Papers
Contents of Collection
- Corporate Events, 1890-1997 and undated, (5 boxes)
  Consists of photographs of official meetings and events that have corporate-wide significance: management meetings; major training seminars; anniversaries and retirement parties of key executives; and corporate mergers. Also includes limited photographs of art items owned by JWT, and of historical artifacts held by the JWT Archives.
  Arranged into Artifacts and Publications; Corporate Artwork; Meetings; Programs; Seminars; Corporate Expansion; and Recognition Events. Order reflects original order of series as received from JWT Archives. Corresponding negatives have been moved to the Negatives Series and noted in the container list.
  - Artifacts and Publications, 1890-1964 and undated
    - Artifacts
      - Change purse, 1900s (Box CE1)
      - Commemorative bowl from Irving Trust, circa 1964 (Box CE1)
      - Glue pot cover, 1900s (Box CE1)
      - Images of J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box CE1)
      - Letter from J. Walter Thompson, 1898 (Box CE1)
      - Medallion, JWT Rosette, 1960s (Box CE1)
      - Medallion, Races of Man, circa 1964 (Box CE1)
      - Pin box, 1890s (Box CE1)
      - Pocket speller, 1890s (Box CE1)
      - T-Square, circa 1960 (Box CE1)
      - Tankard, 1964 (Box CE1)
    - Publications
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising, 1897 (Box CE1)
      - JWT first television advertising news item, 1930 (Box CE1)
      - Unknown, centerfold, circa 1930 (Box CE1)
  - Corporate Artwork, 1905-1969 and undated
    - Art Acquired by JWT
      - Epstein, Joseph. Old Pinager, 1923. Acquired 1961 (Box CE2)
      - Mackendrick, Lilian. Still Life with Lobster, undated (Box CE2)
      - Maillol, Aristide. Acquired after 1969 (Box CE2)
      - Moore, Henry. Helmet sculpture (Box CE2)
      - Picasso, Pablo. Harlequin bronze sculpture, 1905 (Box CE2)
      - Prendergast, Maurice. Train Rides, circa 1964 (Box CE2)
      - Senior, Rai (Raimond) (Box CE2)
      - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri. Moulin Rouge La Gulue, undated. Acquired 1965 (Box CE2)
    - Art Exhibitions
      - Group Shows
        - Craftsmen--Wall Hanging, 1967-1968 (Box CE2)
        - Federation of Modern Painters and Sculptors, 1965-1966 (Box CE2)
        - Lithographs from the Hollander Workshop, circa 1965 (Box CE2)
        - Loan Show from the private collection of Dene Ulin, 1964-1965 (Box CE2)
        - New York Society of Women Artists, Inc., 1965 (Box CE2)
        - Polish Artists, 1966 (Box CE2)
        - Silvermine Guild of Artists, Inc., 1964 (Box CE2)
      - Single Artists
        - Balossi, John, 1966 (Box CE2)
        - Everett, Walker G., 1965 (Box CE2)
        - Forman, Alice, 1966 (Box CE2)
        - Ikeda, Masuo, circa 1965 (Box CE2)
        - King, William, 1966 (Box CE2)
        - O'Donnell, Bill, 1966 (Box CE2)
        - Reed, Susan, 1965 (Box CE2)
  - Corporate Expansion, 1969-1985
    - Acquisition (Box CE3)
      - Lord, Geller, Federico, Peterson, Inc., 1973 (Box CE3)
      - World Wide Agency, 1979 (Box CE3)
    - JWT Stock Exchange Listings
      - London, 1983 (Box CE3)
      - New York, 1969 (Box CE3)
    - Merger
      - Axiom Market--Research Bureaus with Simmons and Associated Research Inc., 1978 (Box CE3)
      - JWT and G.D.D (Spain), 1985 (Box CE3)
      - Marti-Flores-Prieto with JWT, 1978 (Box CE3)
  - Meetings, 1960-1994 and undated
    - Annual--New York, 1970-1980, (6 folders) (Box CE3)
    - Asia-Pacific Managers, Philippines--Manila, 1985 (Box CE3)
    - Board of Directors
      - Chicago, 1961 (Box CE3)
      - London, 1967, (3 folders) (Box CE3)
      - New York, 1964-1984, (6 folders) (Box CE3)
    - Board of Directors (Canadian), Canada--Vancouver, 1968 (Box CE3)
    - Board of Directors (retired) Dinners, New York, 1976 (Box CE3)
    - Commodore Club, Spain, 1994 (Box CE3)
    - European Managers
      - Austria--Vienna, 1965 (Box CE3)
      - Austria--Vienna, 1975 (Box CE3)
      - England--London, 1961 (Box CE3)
      - Germany--Frankfurt, 1973 (Box CE3)
      - Germany--Hamburg, 1985 (Box CE3)
      - Holland--Amsterdam, 1966 (Box CE3)
      - Italy--Milan, 1960 (Box CE3)
      - Portugal--Lisbon, 1972 (Box CE3)
      - Spain--Madrid, 1969 (Box CE3)
      - Spain--Palma di Majorca, 1977 (Box CE3)
      - United States--Detroit, 1964 (Box CE3)
      - United States--New York, 1964 (Box CE3)
      - Venezuela--Caracas, circa 1986 (Box CE3)
    - EROC Meeting, Spain--Madrid, 1981 (Box CE3)
    - Financial Managers Meeting, unknown, undated (Box CE3)
    - First Executive Session on AAAA, unknown, 1917-1918 (Box CE3)
    - Latin American Managers
      - Argentina--Buenos Aires, 1984 (Box CE3)
      - Brazil--São Paulo, 1962, 1984, (2 folders) (Box CE3)
      - Mexico--Mexico City, 1966 (Box CE3)
      - United States--New York, circa 1964, 1968, (2 folders) (Box CE3)
      - Venezuela--Caracas, circa 1972-1974 (Box CE3)
      - Unknown, 1963 (Box CE3)
    - Security Analysts Meeting, New York, 1976 (Box CE3)
    - Stockholders Meeting, New York, 1975 (Box CE3)
    - Thompson Recruitment Meeting, New York, 1984 (Box CE3)
    - Unidentified event photographs, undated (Box CE3)
    - [U.S. Professionals Conference, Glen Cove, NY, 1978: See Oversize Materials] (Box CE3)
    - World-Wide Managers (Box CE4)
      - Germany--Frankfurt, 1963 (Box CE4)
      - United States--New York, 1978 (Box CE4)
      - United States--Orlando, 1984
        - General (Box CE4)
        - Epcot Swap Shop, circa 1984, (3 folders) (Box CE4)
  - Programs, 1962-1997 and undated
    - 4-H Congress, unknown, 1960 (Box CE4)
    - Advertising Hall of Fame Luncheon, unknown, 1986, (2 folders) (Box CE4)
    - Board of Directors Dinner, England--London, 1977, (2 folders) (Box CE4)
    - Corporate Orientation, New York, 1980 (Box CE4)
    - Dinner for European Managers and New York Board, London, 1977 (Box CE4)
    - Dinner for the Resors, unknown, 1962 (Box CE4)
    - Evening at Emory--Advertising for the New Professional, Atlanta, 1983 (Box CE4)
    - Financial Managers Cocktail Party, unknown, undated (Box CE4)
    - Global Media Council Workshop, unknown, 1997 (Box CE4)
    - Il Futuro Della Communicazione Convention, Milan, 1985, (2 folders) (Box CE4)
    - JWT Archives transfer to Duke University--Robert Byrd, Cynthia Swank, unidentified man, circa 1987 (Box CE4)
    - JWT Global Media Group Visit to Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1997, (2 folders) (Box CE4)
    - Ladies Luncheon, unknown, undated (Box CE4)
    - Management Development, Troutbeck, N.Y., 1982, (2 folders) (Box CE4)
    - Martin Scorcese Speaks to Creative, New York, 1985 (Box CE4)
    - Semi Annual Review--Public Relations Managers, San Francisco, 1968 (Box CE4)
    - Sven Mohr Party, unknown, undated (Box CE4)
    - Visit to Duke University, Durham, N.C., undated (Box CE4)
  - Recognition Events, 1959-1994
    - Anniversary
      - 100th Anniversary Silver Bowl, 1964 (Box CE4)
      - 125th Anniversary Party, 1989 (Box CE4)
      - Chase and Sandborn 102nd Anniversary Show, 1966 (Box CE4)
      - Young, James Webb (50th Anniversary), 1961, (5 folders) (Box CE4)
    - Awards (Box CE5)
      - Chairman's Award, 1984 (Box CE5)
      - Creative Awards, 1984, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
      - Gold Effie, 1994 (Box CE5)
      - [White Pea Awards, 1987; See Oversized Materials] (Box CE5)
    - Retirement
      - Hinks, Kennett, 1963 (Box CE5)
      - Resor, Stanley, 1961, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
      - Saunders, Douglas, 1959 (Box CE5)
  - Seminars, 1967-1986
    - European Advertising
      - Amsterdam, 1968 (Box CE5)
      - Frankfurt, 1967 (Box CE5)
    - General Development, New York, 1981 (Box CE5)
    - James Webb Young Seminar
      - Chicago, 1977 (Box CE5)
      - Delevan, Wisc., 1977 (Box CE5)
      - Lima, 1979-1984, (4 folders) (Box CE5)
      - Philippines, 1982 (Box CE5)
      - Segovia, 1981-1983, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
      - Unknown, 1978, 1980, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
    - JWT International Seminar, Holland--Noordwijk, 1969, 1974-1980, (5 folders) (Box CE5)
    - Sam Meek Seminar
      - Napa Valley, Calif., 1985, 1986, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
      - São Paulo, 1981 (Box CE5)
      - Stresa, 1980 (Box CE5)
      - Tokyo, 1984 (Box CE5)
    - World Wide Creative
      - Bermuda, 1981 (Box CE5)
      - Cancun, 1983 (Box CE5)
    - Young Tigers Seminar, Hangzhou, China, 1994, (2 folders) (Box CE5)
- Office Photographs Series, 1889-1997 and undated, (25 boxes)
  Contains photographs of exteriors and interiors of buildings housing JWT offices around the world; office activities such as employee events, outings, and celebrations; and client related activities. Organized into U.S. and International categories. The U.S. offices are organized with New York first, followed by Chicago and then the rest of the U.S. offices listed alphabetically. International offices are organized alphabetically by country and city. Corresponding negatives have been moved to the Negatives Series and noted in the container list.
  - New York Office
    [Includes photographs of all the buildings the office has occupied: 244 Madison Avenue (1918); 41 Park Row; East 23rd Street; the Graybar Building (420 Lexington Avenue); 466 Lexington Avenue. Also includes photographs of Charles Sheeler-designed Colonial/New England dining room (1923); Samuel Yellin's iron grillwork (circa 1920s).]
    - Buildings
      - General
        - 38 Park Row--Exterior, 1889 (Box OF1)
          [Negative available]
        - 41 Park Row--Exterior, 1891 (Box OF1)
        - 44-60 East Twenty-Third Street--Exterior, 1905 (Box OF1)
      - 244 Madison Avenue
        - Colonial Dining Room, 1923 (Box OF1)
        - Exterior, 1917 (Box OF1)
        - Interior views, 1918 (Box OF1)
        - Interior views, Artist's studio, 1918 (Box OF1)
        - Office views, 1918 (Box OF1)
        - Other views, 1918, (12 folders) (Box OF1)
        - 380 Hudson Street warehouse, 1983 (Box OF1)
      - 466 Lexington Avenue
        - Exterior, 1970s (Box OF2)
        - Exterior, undated (Box OF2)
        - Exterior--Renovation, 1979 (Box OF2)
        - Exterior--Renovation, 1979 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Archives, 1980-1986 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Archives Department, 1986 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Architect's model, 1979 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1981 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Mock-up, 1981 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Office--Art Director mock-up, 1981 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Office--Johnston, Don, 1986 (Box OF2)
        - Interior--Office--Lanigan, Denis, 1986 (Box OF2)
        - Model, 1979 (Box OF2)
      - Entertainment Group (1500 Broadway), undated
        - Exterior, undated (Box OF2)
        - Offices, undated (Box OF2)
      - Graybar Building
        - Archives, 1980 (Box OF3)
        - Exterior, 1927-1980 (Box OF3)
        - Exterior, 1980 (Box OF3)
        - Interior, 1929 (Box OF3)
        - Interior, 1963 (Box OF3)
        - Interior, 1979 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Board Room, 1973 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1984 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1960s (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Colonial Dining Room--Bottle Collection, 1960s (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Public Relation-Publicity Department, 1947 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Research Kitchen, 1920s (Box OF3)
        - Interior--T.V. Workshop, 1955 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--T.V. Workshop, 1955 (Box OF3)
        - Interior--Yellin's History of Printing, 1929 (Box OF3)
        - Communications Center, 1968 June 25 (Box OF4)
        - Creative Library, 1979 (Box OF4)
        - Information Center, 1964 (Box OF4)
        - Information Center, 1967 (Box OF4)
        - Information Center, 1968 Mar. (Box OF4)
        - Information Center, 1975 (Box OF4)
        - Lecture Hall, 1930s (Box OF4)
        - Lecture Hall, 1964 (Box OF4)
        - Lidor Mural, 1964 (Box OF4)
        - Media Department, 1920s (Box OF4)
        - Michael's Pillar, 1971 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Brundage, Howard, 1963 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Group Head Women's Copy, 1920s (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Kohl, Howard, 1960s (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Kohl, Howard, 1963 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Meek, Samuel W., 1947 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Resor, Stanley, 1920s (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Richey, Hunter, 1920s (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Seymour, Dan, 1963-1965 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Strouse, Norman, 1965 (Box OF4)
        - Offices--Wilson, E.G., 1963 (Box OF4)
        - Reception area, 1929 (Box OF4)
        - Reception area, 1940s (Box OF4)
        - Reception area, 1945 (Box OF4)
        - Reception area, 1963 (Box OF4)
        - Reception area--Lippold Sculpture, 1960s (Box OF4)
        - Reception area--proposed carpeting, 1978 (Box OF4)
        - Reception area--remodeling (11th floor), 1978 (Box OF4)
        - Renovation, 1963 (Box OF4)
        - Reproduction Department, 1971 (Box OF4)
        - Telephone Operators, 1971 (Box OF4)
        - Telephone Room, 1966 (Box OF4)
        - T.V. Workshop, 1955 (Box OF4)
        - Olympia Apartment, 1964 June (Box OF4)
    - Clients
      - Allegheny Airlines T.V. commercial, 1976 (Box OF5)
      - American Red Cross, 1982 (Box OF5)
      - Anthracite Institute, circa 1940s (Box OF5)
      - Blue Cross, 1954 (Box OF5)
      - Burger King, 1976-1984 (Box OF5)
      - Congoleum
        - General, 1969 (Box OF5)
        - Display, undated (Box OF5)
        - The Wiz poster, undated (Box OF5)
      - Eastman Kodak (Box OF6)
        - General, 1954-56 (Box OF6)
        - General, 1957 June 11 (Box OF6)
        - Anniversary, 1980 (Box OF6)
        - Bicentennial campaign, 1976 Apr. 14 (Box OF6)
        - Billboards, 1970s (Box OF6)
        - Disney endorsement. 1959 Disneyland additions, 1959, 1965 (Box OF6)
        - Grand Central Station colorama, 1980 Feb. (Box OF6)
        - Instamatic model poses, 1964, (3 folders) (Box OF6)
        - Marvin Hamlisch and Dave Perry (JWT), 1974 (Box OF6)
        - Michael Landon, 1978 (Box OF6)
        - Scenes from Turn Around commercial, 1963 (Box OF6)
        - Television commercial shoot, 1977 (Box OF6)
        - Florida Citrus Commission campaign, 1950 (Box OF6)
      - Ford, 1957-1975, (14 folders) (Box OF6)
      - Ford (continued), 1974-1978, (7 folders) (Box OF8)
      - Ford--Charles Schultz, with drawing of Charlie Brown, 1959 (Box OF8)
      - Ford television, 1950s (Box OF8)
      - Goodyear photographs of billboard, 1984 (Box OF8)
      - Kellogg's Rice Krispies, undated (Box OF8)
      - Lever Brothers--Anniversary, 1980 (Box OF8)
      - Lever Brothers--Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Apr. (Box OF8)
      - La Prada, undated (Box OF8)
      - Libby, California Fruit, 1910s (Box OF8)
      - [Liggett and Myers: See Oversize Materials] (Box OF8)
      - [New York Central Railroad: See Oversize Materials] (Box OF8)
      - Pan Am, 1960s (Box OF8)
      - Pan Am JWT centennial Allegheny Airlines, 1964 (Box OF8)
      - Parker, Quink, 1940s (Box OF8)
      - Phillips Petroleum Co. Filming of television commercial, 1966 (Box OF8)
      - Radio Corp of America Graphic Division, Warhol Pig, 1967 Jan. (Box OF8)
      - RCA (Color Trak TV commercial), 1975 Dec. (Box OF8)
      - Reader's Digest
        - Filming commercial, 1980 (Box OF9)
        - Gun control, 1965 June (Box OF9)
        - Physical fitness demonstrations, 1964 Oct. (Box OF9)
        - The New Religion meeting, 1968 Jan. 31 (Box OF9)
      - Red Cross, 1958 (Box OF9)
      - Religion in American Life--Banquet, 1967 Apr. 12 (Box OF9)
      - Religion in American Life--Billboard, 1969-1970 (Box OF9)
      - S.T.P. Oil and Gas Treatment commercial/ Robert Blake, 1970s (Box OF9)
      - Salvation Army
        - Medallion exchange, 1965 June 4 (Box OF9)
        - New York Times Supplement, 1969 (Box OF9)
        - New York Times Supplement, 1969 Nov. (Box OF9)
        - Sculpture, 1968 June 13 (Box OF9)
      - Samsonite, 1976-1977 (Box OF9)
      - Scott Paper (Radio-TV), mid 1950s (Box OF9)
      - Shell--City of Tomorrow, American Red Cross, 1937 (Box OF9)
      - Simmons Mattress commercial, 1974 (Box OF9)
      - Singer fashion show, 1960s (Box OF9)
      - Standard Brands
        - H.V. Kaltern born. Edits the News Radio-T.V. Department, 1950s (Box OF9)
        - Reggie candy, 1979 (Box OF9)
        - Republican National Convention, 1968 (Box OF9)
        - The Chase and Sanborn 101st Anniversary Show Presents Edgar Berger and Charlie McCarthy, 1965 Nov. (Box OF9)
      - Swift's Easter ham and bacon, 1910s (Box OF9)
      - Toys 'R' Us, 1982 (Box OF9)
      - United States Marine Corps--Filming commercial, 1980 (Box OF9)
      - U.S. Playing Cards--Billboards, 1957 (Box OF9)
      - World's Fair, 1964-65 (Box OF9)
    - Events
      - Advertising Hall of Fame induction ceremonies, 1979 (Box OF10)
      - Advertising Hall of Fame (Sam Meek), 1986 (Box OF10)
      - Advertising Marketing Intelligence, 1980 (Box OF10)